<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="LabelHelp">FAQs</string>

    <!--Questions-->
    <string name="Ques1"><b>1. What makes this application better from others in the Market?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques2"><b>2. How can I Contribute to make this app better ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques3"><b>3. Why do i get weird numbers with \'E\' between them ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques4"><b>4. I Found a Bug, Where to Report?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques5"><b>5. I think that "blah..blah" Operation is missing ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques6"><b>6. How can i contact You apart from github and mails ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques7"><b>7. Why do you use ..3101 everywhere ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques8"><b>8. Why Can\'t I save a Matrix Result involving Exponents ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques9"><b>9. Is there any Hope to get Support for Imaginary Numbers ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques10"><b>10. I just Loved your Work, How can i Support You ? </b></string>

    <!--Answers-->
    <string name="Answer1"><b>This is a Open Source Project</b>, Hence Unique in itself.</string>
    <string name="Answer2">This is an Open Source Application and Everyone can contribute to make it better.
        Here is my Repository <u>https://www.github.com/coder3101</u> .</string>
    <string name="Answer3">The Numbers involving \'E\' are not weird but, another way of representing
        bigger numbers in Scientific Notation. For Example if Your result is something like
        \"1.234568245E14\", it means 1.234568245 x 10^14.</string>
    <string name="Answer4">If You are an Open Source Project Contributor. You can report problems on github and we will sort it out.
        Alternatively, You can write to me through Feedback Section of the Application. Or Last but not least you can write issues in Play store Review Page. </string>
    <string name="Answer5">I Included most of the Operations (still in Standard 12 did n\'t studied more than this).
    If You think Some Operations are Missing, Please Let me Know. I will try my best to
        include them in next versions of the app. (Yeah.. I will also get the opportunity to learn new Operations)</string>
    <string name="Answer6">There are many ways to contact me, like you can reach to me on facebook here <u>https://www.facebook.com/coder3101</u></string>
    <string name="Answer7">Hey, its my birthday 31 January. Just a new way to let the World know \"I was born on this date\".</string>
    <string name="Answer8">The Matrix Result involving Exponents can\'t be saved as a new Variable because,
        The Highest number a Cell in the Matrix can hold is <b>999999</b>.
        It can hold up to <b>99999999</b>, if \"Extra Small Font\" is allowed in Settings.</string>
    <string name="Answer9">I am currently working on to bring it. But for that it needs a different
        keyboard etc, so it may take some time but sooner or later it will be added. Also i am Planning to
        add Support for Trigonometric Ratios.</string>
    <string name="Answer10"><b>Share my work</b></string>
</resources>