<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="LabelHelp">FAQs</string>

    <!--Questions-->
    <string name="Ques1"><b>What makes this application better from others in the Market?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques2"><b>How can I Contribute to make this app better ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques3"><b>Why do i get weird numbers with \'E\' between them ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques4"><b>I don\'t like the Advertisement, and i don\'t have money also. Is there any Good News for me ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques5"><b>I think that "blah..blah" Opertion is missing ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques6"><b>How can i contact You apart from github and mails ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques7"><b>Why do you use ..3101 everywhere ?</b></string>

    <!--Answers-->
    <string name="Answer1">The Application in itself is Unique, it has many features such as Dark Theme, etc..
        which makes it different from others in the market. Moreover
        <b>This is a Open Source Project, Hence Unique in itself</b></string>
    <string name="Answer2">The Application is Open Source and the best thing about a OpenSource Projects are that,
        every individual who knows even a bit of Programming can contribute to make it better.
        Here is my Repository <u>https://www.github.com/coder3101</u> I invite you to help me built it better for You.</string>
    <string name="Answer3">The Number involving \'E\' is not Weird but is actually another way of representing
        bigger numbers in Scientific Notation. For Example if Your result is something like
        \"1.234568245E14\", it means 1.234568245 x 10^14.</string>
    <string name="Answer4">Those Advertisements may annoy you, but they are a Source of Earning for me.. but fortuntely, i like talents
    and i hate if money comes in between you and your goals, So Guess What, You can still have the Paid Version of the App for free, but
    since nothing is actually free so you will have to do something, you will have to compile the complete application by your ownself, Clone the Project and cook it.
    Please Do not share your cooked Applications with others, let them compile their own..</string>
    <string name="Answer5">Well i Just Included all the Operations which i know (still in Class 12 didn\'t studied more than this).
    If You think that Some Operations are Missing then Please Let me Know, I will try my best to
        include that in next versions of the app. (Yeah I will also get opportunity to learn new Operations also)</string>
    <string name="Answer6">I mean that there are many ways to contact me, like you can reach to me on facebook here <u>https://www.facebook.com/coder3101</u></string>
    <string name="Answer7">Hey, its my birthday 31 January. Just a new way to let the World know, that i was born on this date.</string>
</resources>