<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="LabelHelp">FAQs</string>

    <!--Questions-->
    <string name="Ques1"><b>1. What makes this application better from others in the Market?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques2"><b>2. How can I Contribute to make this app better ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques3"><b>3. Why do i get weird numbers with \'E\' between them ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques5"><b>4. I think that "blah..blah" Operation is missing ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques8"><b>5. Why Can\'t I save a Matrix Result involving Exponents ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques9"><b>6. Is there any Hope to get Support for Imaginary Numbers ?</b></string>
    <string name="Ques10"><b>7. I Found a Bug, Where to Report? </b></string>

    <!--Answers-->
    <string name="Answer1"><b>This is an Open Source Project</b>, Unique in itself.</string>

    <string name="Answer2">The Application is an Open Source Project So Everyone can contribute to make it better.
        Here is my Repository <u>https://www.github.com/coder3101</u>. I invite you to help me making it better for You.</string>

    <string name="Answer3">The Numbers involving \'E\' are not weird but another way of representing
        bigger numbers in Scientific Notation. For Example if Your result is something like
        \"1.234568245E14\", it means 1.234568245 x 10^14.</string>

    <string name="Answer5">I Included all the Operations (still in Class 12 didn\'t studied more than this).
    If You think that Some Operations are Missing, Please Let me Know. I will try my best to
        include them in next versions of the app.</string>
    <string name="Answer8">The Matrix Result involving Exponents can\'t be saved as a new Variable because,
        The Highest number which a Cell in the Matrix can hold is <b>999999</b>.
        It can hold up to <b>99999999</b>, if \"Extra Small Font\" is allowed in Settings. <b>Only Available in Pro Version</b></string>
    <string name="Answer9">I am currently working on to bring it. But for that it needs a different
        keyboard etc, so it may take some time but sooner or later it will be added. I am also Planning to
        add Support for Trigonometric Ratios.</string>
    <string name="Answer10">If you are a OpenSource Contributor, you can report the same on github.
        Or You can report the Problem on Google Playstore Review Page. I will be Happy to listen to your Valuable FeedBack.</string>
</resources>